<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>0x15AAC</title><link>https://isaacparker.co/</link><description>Recent content on 0x15AAC</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>&amp;copy; 2022 Isaac Parker</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 10:44:12 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://isaacparker.co/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>New Site, First Post, What's New?</title><link>https://isaacparker.co/posts/new-site-first-post-whats-new/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 10:44:12 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://isaacparker.co/posts/new-site-first-post-whats-new/</guid><description>Hey there internet friend! I decided to re-launch my site using Hugo. After writing a little blog site in 2017 and then promptly forgetting about it, I&amp;rsquo;m back to actually be productive in writing posts :D
It turns out that running a full VM with a PostgreSQL database and multiple Docker containers may not be necessary to serve highly static content!
K.I.S.S.</description></item><item><title>About Isaac Parker</title><link>https://isaacparker.co/about/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://isaacparker.co/about/</guid><description>Email Me: parrotmac@gmail.com
About Me I like to make things! At the moment, some of my interests (in no particular order) include&amp;hellip;
Electronics (PCB Design, Embedded Communication Protocols) CAN Bus :heart: Operating System &amp;amp; Networking Internals (Linux, FreeBSD, [Writing an OS in Rust series][https://os.phil-opp.com/]) iptables -&amp;gt; nftables eBPF UEFI Wireguard Filesystems (ZFS) Self-hosting Proxmox CNC Machining (Wood, Soft Metals) 3D Printing (PLA, ABS) Welding (a grinder and paint makes me the welder I ain&amp;rsquo;t!</description></item><item><title>A (Not So) Brief Overview Of This Site's Setup</title><link>https://isaacparker.co/posts/ported-first-post/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2017 22:40:00 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://isaacparker.co/posts/ported-first-post/</guid><description>Editor&amp;rsquo;s Note: This was originally posted on my previous blog platform. While building that site was a great personal learning experience, it wasn&amp;rsquo;t totally practical to maintain and has since been replaced.
It seems only fitting to have the first post of a self-built blog to be about, well, the blog! I&amp;rsquo;ll list the technologies I used and why I chose them. In a later post I&amp;rsquo;ll cover details on how I put them together.</description></item></channel></rss>